ALEXIS MITZAEL PADILLA

Cell: (712) 577-1336

Email: padillalT@outlook.com

SUMMARY

Experienced networking and web design professional, with a developing skillset in cybersecurity practices. Proficient in multiple programing languages. Significant familiarity with administrative support, client relations, account management, and project management. Fluent Native Spanish and English speaker.

EDUCATION

Associates Degree, Northeast Community College, Norfolk, NE May 2017 Bachelor of Science, Computer Information Systems, Web Analyst, Wayne State College, Wayne, NE, May 2020 Cyber Security Labs

Cybint Cybersecurity Bootcamp May 2020

SKILLS/TOOLS

Operating Systems

Mac OS

Windows OS

Linux OS

Programing

Java

MySQL

HTL/CSS

Cybersecurity

Wireshark

Splunk

FTK, Autopsy, and Scalpel

Nmap

Snort

Metasploit

Web Scraping

Kibana

Active Directory

EXPERIENCE

Freelance Web Designer/Graphic designer, Aug 2021 - Present

- Design HTML and CSS websites from scratch
- Logo design for personal and client use
- WordPress and Wix

Service Center Specialist, College Center, Sep 2020 - Dec, 2021

- Provide technical assistance and support for incoming queries and issues related to computer systems, software, and hardware.
- Run diagnostic programs to resolve problems
- Respond to email messages for customers seeking help.
- Ask questions to determine nature of problem.
- Follow up with customers to ensure issue has been resolved

IT Support Agent Consultant/ Sales Associate, Best Buy, Sioux City, IA, Sept. 2015-Oct. 2019

- Provided technical assistance and support for customer issues related to computer systems, software and hardware
- Responded to customers in-person or over the phone seeking help with their electronics
- Installed, handled troubleshooting and resolved computer hardware/software issues
- Configured computers systems, diagnosing hardware/software faults
- Provided orientation and guidance to users on how to operate new software and computer equipment